<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>Properties &#8211; Image Property</title>
	<atom:link href="https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://imageproperty.com.au</link>
	<description>Brisbane&#039;s premier property management and sales team - specialising in all property services and focus on our relationships and internal processes to ensure a valuable customer experience, whether you&#039;re an investor, vendor or tenant.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 08:06:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-AU</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://imageproperty.com.au/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/favicon-image-property.png</url>
	<title>Properties &#8211; Image Property</title>
	<link>https://imageproperty.com.au</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>19 Duke Street, Brighton  QLD  4017</title>
		<link>https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/19-duke-street-brighton-qld-4017/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Image Property Management]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 08:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/19-duke-street-brighton-qld-4017/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On the market for the first time in decades, don&#8217;t...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On the market for the first time in decades, don&#8217;t miss the chance to secure this rare opportunity! </p>
<p>Imagine the endless possibilities with this prime piece of Brighton real estate &#8211; set on 422m2 &#038; walking distance to the waterfront &#8211; bring the home back to its former glory or build the family home of your dreams!</p>
<p>Located in a quiet street in the heart of Brighton with local to shops, parks, schools and public transport, convenience is covered!</p>
<p>Separate kitchen with eat-in dining and lounge room, there is so much you could do to make this your dream home.</p>
<p>Featuring- </p>
<p>&#8211; Fully fenced 422m2 block<br />
&#8211; 9.9 M frontage<br />
&#8211; 2 generously sized bedrooms<br />
&#8211; Spacious living room and eat in kitchen<br />
&#8211; Bathroom with shower and separate toilet<br />
&#8211; Laundry<br />
&#8211; Single Carport and verandah<br />
&#8211; Shed<br />
&#8211; Solar  </p>
<p>So Close to:</p>
<p>&#8211; Sandgate, the cutest bayside village centre in greater Brisbane<br />
&#8211; Bike and footpaths stretching the length of the waterfront linking to parks, nature reserves, cafés, a brand-new aquatic centre and historic Shorncliffe jetty<br />
&#8211; Specialty stores and all key services<br />
&#8211; Endless cafés, coffee shops and restaurants<br />
&#8211; Public and private schools<br />
&#8211; Public transport and easy access to the M1.<br />
&#8211; Sandgate dining shopping precinct and Sandgate Train Station for the short commute to Brisbane city, is 5 minutes by car.<br />
&#8211; Brisbane Airport is 20 minutes by car</p>
<p>Walk to the waterfront &#038; jog along Flinders Parade. Enjoy a stroll to the many beautiful local cafes Sandgate has to offer. </p>
<p>Please contact me for all further enquiries &#038; to arrange your inspection.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>9/86 Brighton Road, Sandgate  QLD  4017</title>
		<link>https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/9-86-brighton-road-sandgate-qld-4017/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Image Property Management]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 07:42:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/9-86-brighton-road-sandgate-qld-4017/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Looking to comfortably live in Sandgate and be a part...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Looking to comfortably live in Sandgate and be a part of our Village? Looking for a fabulous, modern, spacious, light filled, private, quiet home?</p>
<p>Look no further, here it is!</p>
<p>Perfectly located in the highly desirable suburb of Sandgate, with all amenities, boutique restaurants, to die for coffee shops and much more, all at your doorstep. And with the added bonus of less than 400 metres to the Sandgate foreshore. </p>
<p>This low maintenance two-bedroom unit is new to the market and will not last long!</p>
<p>This very spacious second floor unit feels bright and airy with plenty of natural light that pours in through the glass sliding doors from the front balcony.</p>
<p>Featuring an open plan living and dining area, that is perfectly positioned around the kitchen, making this unit great for entertaining. </p>
<p>The kitchen is excellent size with loads of storage, stone benchtops, breakfast bar, stainless steel appliances, dishwasher, and plenty of cupboard space. </p>
<p>At the rear of the unit is the master bedroom featuring an impressive sized ensuite with double vanity sinks, built in wardrobe and second balcony that away from any street noise and very private. </p>
<p>Featuring a second bedroom serviced by the family size bathroom, including shower over bath and second toilet. </p>
<p>Also Featuring:</p>
<p>&#8211; Second Floor Unit<br />
&#8211; Modern Kitchen with Stone Benchtops<br />
&#8211; Great Location<br />
&#8211; Air-Conditioning<br />
&#8211; Two Balconies<br />
&#8211; Laundry in Cupboard<br />
&#8211; Secure Garage Space<br />
&#8211; Fully Sealed Storage Cage</p>
<p>So Close to:</p>
<p>&#8211; Bike and footpaths stretching the length of the waterfront linking to parks, nature reserves cafés, a brand-new aquatic centre and historic Shorncliffe jetty<br />
&#8211; Specialty stores and all key services<br />
&#8211; Endless cafés, coffee shops and restaurants<br />
&#8211; Public and private schools<br />
&#8211; Public transport and easy access to the M1<br />
&#8211; Sandgate dining shopping precinct and Sandgate Train Station for the short commute to Brisbane city is at your doorstep<br />
&#8211; Brisbane Airport is 10 minutes by car</p>
<p>Don&#8217;t miss your chance to experience the great lifestyle that Sandgate has to offer and call to book your inspection today.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>9 Georgia Street, Caboolture South  QLD  4510</title>
		<link>https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/9-georgia-street-caboolture-south-qld-4510/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Image Property Management]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 02:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/9-georgia-street-caboolture-south-qld-4510/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Viewing By Private Inspection Only. The elegant and beautiful street...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Viewing By Private Inspection Only. </p>
<p>The elegant and beautiful street appeal of this newly built, 4-bedroom home hints at the caliber you&#8217;ll find.  As you step through the front entrance, you&#8217;ll discover an inviting and stylish ambiance purposefully created with enjoyable, practical and comfortable living in mind.</p>
<p>This superbly designed home with generous dimensions and high quality finishes will appeal to so many people, including first home buyers, down-sizers, up-sizers or investors.</p>
<p>Property Features<br />
•	The kitchen is truly the heart of the home!   Eye catching and stylish with stone bench<br />
        tops, modern appliances, dishwasher and an impressive butler&#8217;s pantry, it overlooks the<br />
        living and dining areas that flow out to the generously sized, tiled alfresco area.<br />
•	Four bedrooms that flow seamlessly with the master featuring a generous walk-in<br />
        wardrobe and en-suite with floor to ceiling tiles, stone bench-top and a double shower.<br />
        The remaining bedrooms have built in robes.<br />
•	Media Room<br />
•	High quality carpets to bedrooms<br />
•	Split Air-conditioning in Family Area and Master Bedroom<br />
•	High Ceilings<br />
•	Double lock up garage<br />
•	Full size internal laundry<br />
•	Linen Cupboards<br />
•	Large tiled alfresco area<br />
•	Low maintenance landscaping.<br />
•	Fully Fenced<br />
•       So Many features and too many to list. </p>
<p>Rental expectation approx. $550 per week<br />
Council rates: approx. $360 per quarter<br />
School catchments: Caboolture State School &#038; Morayfield State High School</p>
<p>Location:<br />
Located in the naturally stunning address of Riverbank Estate surrounded by 60 hectares of park lands, graced with walking and cycling tracks, dog parks, playgrounds, picnic and BBQ spots as well as a community vegetable. This residence is conveniently close to transport, shopping centres and schools and just moments away from home lies a river with serene outlooks and quiet fishing spots. </p>
<p>•	2 min bridge connection to the Bruce Highway<br />
•	Morayfield Shopping Centre (approximately a 3 min drive)<br />
•	Morayfield Train Station (approximately a 4 min drive)<br />
•	Brisbane CBD (approximately a 45 min drive)<br />
•	Brisbane Airport (approximately a 30 min drive)<br />
•	Sunshine Coast (approximately a 35 min drive)</p>
<p>If you&#8217;re ready to invest or move into this very special, sunshine filled home, call Lara on 0404 019 916.</p>
<p>*** Please Note*****:<br />
This Home is approximately 3 to 4 weeks from being completed and photos used are from a similar home that was recently built and sold. Virtual staging has been used in some of the images. </p>
<p>Disclaimer :<br />
Information contained on any marketing material, website or other portal should not be relied upon and you should make your own enquiries and seek your own independent advice with respect to any property advertised or the information about the property.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>103/584 Brunswick Street, New Farm  QLD  4005</title>
		<link>https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/103-584-brunswick-street-new-farm-qld-4005/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Image Property Management]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 02:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/103-584-brunswick-street-new-farm-qld-4005/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Providing a superior lifestyle from its incredibly central location, immerse...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Providing a superior lifestyle from its incredibly central location, immerse yourself in the best that inner-city living has to offer with a huge range of lifestyle, entertainment and shopping precincts at your door! Boasting modern design and offering low-maintenance appeal, there is move-in ready comfort on offer and a vibrant lifestyle for the taking!</p>
<p>Intelligently designed to capture natural light and easy-living, open-plan living and dining is generously sized with ducted air-conditioning providing year-round comfort. Impressing with both functionality and refined design, the modern kitchen offers superb storage within streamlined cabinetry, along with stainless appliance and waterfall stone bench with integrated seating.</p>
<p>Flowing directly from the living space, a covered balcony is ideally sized to extend your living or dining outdoors, capturing good vantage over the leafy landscape and livelihood below.</p>
<p>Two built-in bedrooms are comfortably sized with the master including a walk-in robe and private ensuite. A second bathroom services the other bedroom impeccably, both bathrooms matching in style and provision including glass showers and floor to ceiling tiling. Additional features include a large internal laundry and single secure vehicle accommodation.</p>
<p>Centrally positioned to a massive range of amenities, transport and dining, this light-filled apartment is the ideal choice for professionals wanting a lifestyle locale with low-maintenance, or investors seeking a sure thing! The perfect combination of easy-care and ultimate convenience, it&#8217;s on the doorstep to the vibrant Howard Smith Wharves with a five minute stroll having you at renowned dining venues as well as the meandering riverwalk. There is of course a myriad of additional famed Brisbane landmarks at your door ready for you to embrace wholeheartedly!</p>
<p>&#8211; Modern unit in premier New Farm location<br />
&#8211; Open-plan living and dining with ducted air-conditioning<br />
&#8211; Covered alfresco balcony with leafy outlook<br />
&#8211; Modern kitchen with refined joinery and stone bench with seating<br />
&#8211; Two built-in bedrooms; master including walk-in robe and private ensuite<br />
&#8211; Second full sized bathroom; both bathrooms matching with glass showers and floor to ceiling tiling<br />
&#8211; Large internal laundry<br />
&#8211; Single secure vehicle accommodation<br />
&#8211; Rooftop BBQ area<br />
&#8211; Walk to massive array of famed landmarks including Howard Smith Wharves, New Farm Park &#038; James Street Precinct</p>
<p>Location is everything in real estate, secure your slice of New Farm by booking an inspection with Steven Webster on 0433 984 117</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>4 Wood Crescent, Baringa  QLD  4551</title>
		<link>https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/4-wood-crescent-baringa-qld-4551/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Image Property Management]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 23:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/4-wood-crescent-baringa-qld-4551/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A carefully considered design, sleek contemporary interiors and a peaceful...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A carefully considered design, sleek contemporary interiors and a peaceful sizeable yard unite in this stylish residence to deliver an idyllic family home of space and flexibility. </p>
<p>Brimming with natural light, this home features a clever layout offering open plan living/dining areas with crisp coastal decor, while sliding doors retract to allow a seamless transition to a superb entertainers&#8217; area at the rear. </p>
<p>A gourmet kitchen is equipped with only the highest of quality appliances and abundant cupboard storage including a butler&#8217;s pantry, while there is a media room/home office with darkened themes for the ultimate comfort. </p>
<p>The four bedrooms are all well-proportioned and appointed with wardrobes and ceiling fans, while the master features an ensuite, sizeable walk-in robe and split system air conditioning. Additional features include a bright and airy fully tiled main bathroom, a large laundry with external access and a substantial Double lock up garage. </p>
<p>Boasting an effortless transition from inside living to your very own private sun-soaked alfresco area and flat yard there is ample room for the kids and your fury friends. </p>
<p>With the Baringa State High School, Shopping Centre and and medical facilities now open, this is a great place to live or invest.</p>
<p>This property is ideally located, with only a one hour drive to Brisbane, 30 minute drive to the Sunshine Coast Airport, 12 minute drive to the Sunshine Coast University Hospital, and several pristine beaches nearby. </p>
<p>Features we love:</p>
<p>4 bed | 2 bath | 2 car<br />
Generously scaled layout features open plan living/dining<br />
Effortless flow to outdoor alfresco area<br />
Streamlined kitchen w/ quality appliances<br />
Generous bedrooms with robes<br />
Master with modern ensuite &#038; walk-in robe<br />
2 x Split system air conditioning<br />
Double car garage<br />
Minutes to Baringa shops, schools and the tavern</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>2 Phar Lap Court, Little Mountain  QLD  4551</title>
		<link>https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/2-phar-lap-court-little-mountain-qld-4551/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Image Property Management]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 10:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/2-phar-lap-court-little-mountain-qld-4551/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Kellie Barridge at Image Property is proud to present to...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Kellie Barridge at Image Property is proud to present to the market for the very first time, one of the most impressive homes in the highly sought after Little Mountain.  Featuring multiple spacious living areas, a pristine, sparkling saltwater pool, and a fabulous location close to everything in Caloundra – there&#8217;s nothing left to do at 2 Phar Lap Court, but move in and call it home!</p>
<p>As you arrive at this impressive residence, you are greeted by an immaculately landscaped front lawn that features easy side access. The property is perfectly positioned in a quiet and secluded cul-de-sac, and your privacy is assured as the house itself is situated on a huge 1,580m2 lifestyle block that is surrounded by landscaped gardens.  If that excites you, just wait until you step inside this beautiful home.</p>
<p>The home itself features 4 large bedrooms, a 5th bedroom/study, 2 bathrooms with plenty of storage space, an internal laundry, double lockup garage, an impeccably renovated, light-filled open plan kitchen with impressive stone benchtops and there&#8217;s ample space for a growing family with an additional 3 separate living areas in total – a formal lounge and reception room at the front of the home, a huge living and dining space in the middle and a rumpus/pool room at the rear. From the impressive layout of this home to the spectacularly huge, covered entertainment area outside – you simply need to inspect.</p>
<p>The massive outdoor entertainment area is another one of the WOW factors of this property and overlooks the lush green gardens and gorgeous salt-water swimming pool, which in itself has its own separate party/BBQ area – the perfect place to lounge on those hot summer days and enjoy watching the kids play in the pool. The pool and entertaining area are positioned so well that there&#8217;s still heaps of additional room in the yard for kids and pets to play, and an impressive 2 door shed with 3 phase power out back for your workshop and additional storage.  It is safe to say that 2 Phar Lap Ct is more than a just a home.  It is a lifestyle waiting to be enjoyed.</p>
<p>The property is located within walking distance to local parks, sports fields, corner stores and the local gym, and is within 10 minutes&#8217; drive to all of Caloundra&#8217;s amazing local beaches. Whether it be retail therapy, cafes or restaurants you are after, everything you could possibly need is within close proximity.</p>
<p>Local school catchment area: Prep to Year 12 &#8211; Meridan State College.</p>
<p>Call Kellie Barridge at Image Property today on 0422 617 653 to arrange your inspection.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>9/11 Taigum Place, Taigum  QLD  4018</title>
		<link>https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/9-11-taigum-place-taigum-qld-4018/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Image Property Management]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 09:50:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/9-11-taigum-place-taigum-qld-4018/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Beautifully presented to accommodate a family or couple who loves...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Beautifully presented to accommodate a family or couple who loves to entertain and live in modern comfort and style. Not only is it centrally located for easy access to shops, schools and transport, you will feel like this is one of Taigum&#8217;s well-kept secrets. Full of character and timeless style, this townhouse has unique features that you simply don&#8217;t get anywhere else.  This stunning 3 bed, 2 bath, 1 car home has all the features you require! Situated on a 138m2 block with one of the most spacious patios around, this property is perfect for you and the family to enjoy or add to your investment portfolio in the ever-growing suburb of Taigum. This home will sell fast!</p>
<p>Imagine living in a property with features like these:</p>
<p>•	3 spacious bedrooms<br />
•	Master bedroom has its own ensuite along and a large built in wardrobe.<br />
•	Beautifully open plan kitchen with stainless steel appliances including a dishwasher, oven, induction cooktop, plenty of storage and a generously sized breakfast bar<br />
•	Both bathrooms are in great condition with traditional styling and quality details throughout<br />
•	Access through the dining takes you out onto the well-built, spacious, covered patio.<br />
•	Single car automatic garage with built in laundry and plenty of storage.<br />
•	Bonus split system air-conditioning above the dining room for extra comfort on the hot summer day or warmth on the cold winter nights.<br />
•	NBN ready</p>
<p>Facts</p>
<p>•	Rates – approx. $385 p/qtr<br />
•	Body Corp – approx. $930 p/qtr<br />
•	Utilities – approx. $370 p/qtr<br />
•	Rental appraised at $415p/w to $450p/w</p>
<p>Centrally located and close to:</p>
<p>•	1 min from Taigum Village (650m)<br />
•	2 min away from Taigum State Primary (1.2km)<br />
•	8 min away from Aspley State High School (4.5km)<br />
•	Close to restaurants/cafe&#8217;s/shops<br />
•	Close to public transport; train station (2.3km) and bus stops within walking distance<br />
•	Parks, bicycle and walking tracks near by</p>
<p>This home has been lovingly maintained and is child and pet friendly. There are many lifestyle features not mentioned above which all add to its functionality and liveability. This home is perfect to either raise your family, watch the area grow, reap the rental return or simply enjoy life in the suburbs. Don&#8217;t miss this opportunity to secure this home in this superb location. Contact Sam Tahana today on 0400 047 129.</p>
<p>Disclaimer<br />
This property is being sold without a price and therefore a price guide cannot be provided. The website may have filtered the property into a price bracket for website functionality purposes.</p>
<p>Information contained on any marketing material, website or other portal should not be relied upon and you should make your own enquiries and seek your own independent advice with respect to any property advertised or the information about the property.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>9 Centurion Street, Bridgeman Downs  QLD  4035</title>
		<link>https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/9-centurion-street-bridgeman-downs-qld-4035/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Image Property Management]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 09:50:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/9-centurion-street-bridgeman-downs-qld-4035/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Kellie Barridge at Image Property is proud to present to...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Kellie Barridge at Image Property is proud to present to the market, 9 Centurion Street in Bridgeman Downs.  Featuring multiple spacious living areas, a huge 803m2 block with over 24m road frontage, and a fabulous, flowing layout that has been designed specifically for easy living, you&#8217;ll feel immediately at home in this striking residence.</p>
<p>On arrival, you are greeted by an immaculate front lawn that has been landscaped to perfection. The property is positioned well in a quiet street, and your privacy is assured as the house itself is situated on a huge lifestyle block that is surrounded by lush gardens and made complete by feature stone retaining walls.  </p>
<p>The home itself features 4 large bedrooms, 2 bathrooms, internal laundry, double lockup garage/workshop, an impeccably designed, light-filled kitchen with timber cabinetry and impressive granite benchtops and there&#8217;s ample space for a growing family with 2 separate living areas in total – a formal lounge and reception room at the front of the home and a dining space off the kitchen. From the impressive layout of this home to the spectacularly huge, covered entertainment area outside – you simply need to inspect.</p>
<p>Features:<br />
&#8211; 4 spacious bedrooms, master with ensuite and built-in wardrobes<br />
&#8211; Stunning kitchen with gas cook top, dishwasher and granite bench tops<br />
&#8211; Double lock up garage<br />
&#8211; Air conditioning<br />
&#8211; Security screens<br />
&#8211; Large covered alfresco entertaining area<br />
&#8211; Plenty of off-street parking<br />
&#8211; Solar panels</p>
<p>This property is perfectly situated to take full advantage of the surrounding amenities including Carseldine Woolworths, the Aspley Hypermarket, Westfield Chermside, both Price Charles and St Vincent&#8217;s hospitals, and an assortment of fabulous coffee shops, restaurants, retail stores and parks for the kids to play.</p>
<p>The closest bus stop is just a short 2 minute walk away.</p>
<p>Confirmed School Zones: Bald Hills State School &#038; Aspley State High School</p>
<p>Please contact Kellie Barridge at Image Property on 0422 617 653 to arrange your inspection today!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>21 Thiess Drive, Albany Creek  QLD  4035</title>
		<link>https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/21-thiess-drive-albany-creek-qld-4035/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Image Property Management]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 09:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/21-thiess-drive-albany-creek-qld-4035/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[21 Thiess Drive, Albany Creek. Situated in a peaceful area...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>21 Thiess Drive, Albany Creek.</p>
<p>Situated in a peaceful area of Albany Creek close to the forest reserve, this home has so much to offer.  </p>
<p>The elevated setting gives a picturesque view whilst having the luxury of the cool breeze during summer and warm sunshine during the winter months. </p>
<p>The home boasts multiple living spaces that open to a captivating outdoor entertaining area with modern inground saltwater pool surrounded by high fences, giving you and your loved ones complete privacy to relax or entertain after a long week at work.  </p>
<p>The house is brilliantly laid out over a single level that has just been freshly painted both inside and out and is situated on a generous 728m2 block.  </p>
<p>As you walk in the front door there is the perfect combination of open plan living with slight separation when required. You will experience a seamless flow from dining, kitchen to the second living area and then onto the jaw dropping outdoor entertaining area with an abundance of room to dine, lounge or host family and friends! </p>
<p>Positioned in a highly sought-after location near Bunya State Forest with easy access to public transport, sporting fields, shops, dining, supermarkets, gyms and is in the catchment area for the highly regarded Albany Hills Primary and High Schools, this is a property not to be missed! </p>
<p>So many things to love: </p>
<p>Single level home with highly functional layout<br />
Three bedrooms all with built ins, split system air conditioning plus fans in bedroom 2 and 3<br />
Master overlooks the pool area with ensuite and generous walk in robe<br />
Open plan living space<br />
Spacious kitchen overlooking pool area<br />
Gas cooking and hot water<br />
Large outdoor entertaining area<br />
Modern inground saltwater pool<br />
Low maintenance yard with beautiful gardens at the front and lush greenery at the rear<br />
High fences around the pool providing a fantastic private setting<br />
Solar – 3kw<br />
Electric security gate<br />
Security system with hard drive storage<br />
Double garage<br />
Garden shed for extra storage  </p>
<p>Location Information: </p>
<p>A popular North Brisbane suburb, Albany Creek is just 12km form the CBD! A highly desired destination for families, there are four primary schools, a well renowned high school and multiple child care centres in the district. Brimming with wonderful green public space, parkland and nature reserves, there are also  impressive local amenities providing multiple shopping centres as well as a huge array of restaurants and food outlets.  Direct public transport links to nearby Prince Charles and St Vincents Hospitals, Westfield Chermside and Brisbane CBD.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>9/55 Samford Road, ALDERLEY  QLD  4051</title>
		<link>https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/9-55-samford-road-alderley-qld-4051/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Image Property Management]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 07:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/9-55-samford-road-alderley-qld-4051/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Perfectly positioned within a boutique complex of only 13 apartments,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Perfectly positioned within a boutique complex of only 13 apartments, this spacious and high quality 2 bedroom apartment offers an exceptional investment opportunity or the perfect low maintenance home.</p>
<p>Summary of Features:<br />
&#8211; Generous open plan, air-conditioned living and dining room<br />
&#8211; Modern Kitchen with quality fixtures and fittings<br />
&#8211; Two bedrooms both with build in robes<br />
&#8211; Master Bedroom with Air Conditioning<br />
&#8211; Entertainers balcony<br />
&#8211; Modern bathroom<br />
&#8211; Internal laundry<br />
&#8211; Dedicated car space in secure car park<br />
&#8211; Off street visitors parking<br />
&#8211; Secure building with intercom system</p>
<p>Connectivity &#038; Lifestyle:<br />
&#8211; 14 minute drive to Brisbane CBD<br />
&#8211; 5 minute walk to Alderley Train Station (400m)<br />
&#8211; 2 minute walk to Coles Alderley (180m)<br />
&#8211; 2 minute walk to bus stop</p>
<p>Approximate Costs:<br />
&#8211; Body Corporate Fees: approx. $646 p/q<br />
&#8211; Rates: approx. $509 p/q<br />
&#8211; Water: approx. $265 p/q</p>
<p>Currently leased for $312/week (NRAS), plus receive a tax free NRAS payment of aprox $11,000 per annum &#8211; Equates to approximately $523 / week! 2 years left on NRAS allocation OR option to remove allocation for owner occupiers/standard investment at no extra cost. Market Rent aprox $390 Per Week.</p>
<p>Please don&#8217;t hesitate to give call if you have any further questions or to book a private appointment.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>1/21 McKillop Street, Rothwell  QLD  4022</title>
		<link>https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/1-21-mckillop-street-rothwell-qld-4022/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Image Property Management]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 06:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/1-21-mckillop-street-rothwell-qld-4022/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Kellie Barridge at Image Property is proud to present to...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Kellie Barridge at Image Property is proud to present to the market, this ultra-modern (just over one year old) immaculately maintained villa. Close to all amenities and located in the heart of the highly coveted suburb of Rothwell, this neat-as-a-pin lowset will appeal to buyers who are looking for an incredibly low maintenance single level home or an investment property in a great area.</p>
<p>Features include:<br />
&#8211; 2 spacious bedrooms, both with built-in wardrobes and ceiling fans<br />
&#8211; Air conditioned living area with ceiling fan<br />
&#8211; A light and bright open plan lounge/dining area<br />
&#8211; A modern gourmet kitchen with stone benchtops and plenty of storage space,  electric cook top, oven and dishwasher<br />
&#8211; Single remote lock-up garage with internal access and plenty of on street parking<br />
&#8211; Security screens throughout<br />
&#8211; Cute side patio/alfresco area with side gate access and a decent sized side yard and garden<br />
&#8211; Garden shed<br />
&#8211; Very low body corporate of approx.. $730.35 per quarter</p>
<p>Positioned within a very tightly held complex that is predominantly owner occupied, the villa is a short walk to the Rothwell Train Station, and Rothwell&#8217;s grocery stores, cafes, restaurants, gyms and retail.  Centrally located is an understatement here, as you are also only a 5 minute drive to the beautiful Redcliffe Peninsula and its beaches, and a 5 minute drive in the opposite direction to the Bruce Highway.</p>
<p>Confirmed School Catchments:<br />
Primary School &#8211; Hercules Rd State School<br />
High School &#8211; Deception Bay State High School<br />
Other local schools &#8211; Southern Cross Catholic Primary School (Kippa-Ring Campus), Mueller College, Grace Lutheran College (Kippa-Ring Campus), St Benedicts College (Mango Hill). </p>
<p>Every now and again something extra special comes along, and this property is certainly an opportunity not to be missed.  For further information or to arrange your inspection, call Kellie Barridge at Image Property today on 0422 617 653.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>3 Mannikin Street, Narangba  QLD  4504</title>
		<link>https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/3-mannikin-street-narangba-qld-4504/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Image Property Management]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 06:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/3-mannikin-street-narangba-qld-4504/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Nestled in the quiet and sought after Creekside Estate, this...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nestled in the quiet and sought after Creekside Estate, this beautiful family home is perched on a generous 900sqm corner block and provides enough space for the family while being in a convenient location with local schools, shops and transport all just minutes away.</p>
<p>This property features:<br />
&#8211; Four well-sized bedrooms all with ceiling fans, built-in wardrobes and ducted air-conditioning. The spacious master bedroom with a walk-in wardrobe and modern ensuite<br />
&#8211; Modern family bathroom with separate bath, shower and toilet<br />
&#8211; Functional and modern kitchen with a breakfast bar, gas cooktop and oven, double sink and plenty of cupboard and bench space<br />
&#8211; Large and open living area with tiled flooring, ceiling fan, ducted air-conditioning and access to your covered entertainment area<br />
&#8211; Family room located at the front of the home with lots of natural light, tiled flooring and ceiling fan and ducted air-conditioning<br />
&#8211; Open dining area with tiled flooring that flows out to your covered entertainment area<br />
&#8211; Ducted air-conditioning<br />
&#8211; High ceilings (9ft)<br />
&#8211; Security screens and blinds throughout</p>
<p>Heading outside, you will find:<br />
&#8211; Covered entertainment area<br />
&#8211; Concreted pergola area<br />
&#8211; 7m x 6m shed<br />
&#8211; Garden shed<br />
&#8211; Water tank<br />
&#8211; Low maintenance gardens<br />
&#8211; Double lock-up remote garage with internal access</p>
<p>Perfectly positioned, close to:<br />
&#8211; Narangba Valley State High School (950m)<br />
&#8211; Local Shopping Centre (1.2km)<br />
&#8211; Narangba Valley State School (1.7km)<br />
&#8211; Burpengary Train Station (5.8km)<br />
&#8211; Access to the Bruce Highway (6.8km)</p>
<p>Call today to secure this property!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>69 Brushbox Street, Taigum  QLD  4018</title>
		<link>https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/69-brushbox-street-taigum-qld-4018/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Image Property Management]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 05:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/69-brushbox-street-taigum-qld-4018/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Auction Location: On-Site Presented to market by the original owners...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Auction Location: On-Site</p>
<p>Presented to market by the original owners of close to 30 years is this Low-Set Taigum masterpiece. A beautifully designed floor plan combined with a recent renovation, this home was built with family living in mind and is not to be missed!</p>
<p>Features include:<br />
&#8211; 690sqm block with landscaped gardens &#038; Side Access<br />
&#8211; Family friendly layout with separate living spaces<br />
&#8211; Tiled flooring throughout<br />
&#8211; Two bathrooms<br />
&#8211; Air Conditioning throughout<br />
&#8211; Solar electricity system<br />
&#8211; Heaps of storage space!</p>
<p>270m2 of home sprawling across one single level, this home offers:</p>
<p>&#8211; 5 large and well-appointed bedrooms<br />
> The master bedroom is located at the rear of the home and is perfect for those who enjoy their own space. Boasting an extra large layout, carpeted flooring, plantation shutters, Mitsubishi air conditioning system, ceiling fan, walk in wardrobe, plus an ensuite<br />
> Bedrooms 2, 3, 4 &#038; 5 enjoy spacious layouts, built in wardrobes, plantation shutters, ceiling fans &#038; carpeted flooring.</p>
<p>&#8211; 2 Family friendly bathrooms<br />
> The master ensuite features large shower, vanity with extra storage, stainless steel fittings &#038; toilet<br />
> The family bathroom features a single basin, large shower, bath, stainless steel fittings &#038; a separate toilet</p>
<p>&#8211; Recently renovated chefs kitchen<br />
> Kleenmaid Ceramic cooktop with large stainless steel rangehood<br />
> Kleenmaid dishwasher<br />
> Plenty of cupboard, drawer &#038; bench space<br />
> 2pac Cabinetry<br />
> 40mm Stone benchtops<br />
> Dual basin sink<br />
> Built in pantry<br />
> Marble tile splashback</p>
<p>&#8211; Multiple living spaces, the best of indoor and outdoor living<br />
> The open plan main living/dining area flows effortlessly to the kitchen and out to the outdoor entertaining area<br />
> The formal living is located towards the front of the home and features carpeted flooring, plantation shutters, ornate cornicing, ceiling rose &#038; glass chandelier<br />
> Outdoor entertaining will be a breeze with the outdoor alfresco area overlooking the large backyard with plenty of space to add a pool.</p>
<p>&#8211; This home also features:<br />
> Recently renovated roof<br />
> Double lock up garage with remote control doors<br />
> Heaps of cupboard storage throughout<br />
> Separate living spaces<br />
> Mitsubishi air conditioning systems<br />
> LED down lights throughout<br />
> Solar power system<br />
> Low maintenance living<br />
> Rear garden shed</p>
<p>&#8211; Amenities nearby:<br />
> Taigum Village shop 1.2km<br />
> Taigum Square Shopping Centre 1.7km<br />
> Taigum State Primary School 2.5km<br />
> Sandgate District High School 3.9km<br />
> Westfield Chermside 6.2km</p>
<p>Homes in Taigum are in high demand! Avoid disappointment and inspect this property for yourself today!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>19 Saul Street, Brighton  QLD  4017</title>
		<link>https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/19-saul-street-brighton-qld-4017/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Image Property Management]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 05:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/19-saul-street-brighton-qld-4017/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Nestled in a sort after pocket of Brighton, this endearing...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nestled in a sort after pocket of Brighton, this endearing home offers a picturesque, green-filled setting boasting all the ambience of bayside living, without the price tag or upkeep! </p>
<p>Within walking distance to the waterfront, sporting, shopping and transport – there is fabulous move-in comfort whilst still offering opportunity for growth, if desired.</p>
<p>Offering classic character street appeal with a quaint entry way, a warm welcome is immediate.<br />
 Freshly painted inside, with floating timber floorboards that flow throughout the interior, opening into a light filled living and dining area boasting a newly updated kitchen which offers superb storage within timeless white cabinetry and extensive bench space.</p>
<p>Positioned on a 655m2 block, the huge backyard is fully fenced and includes mature greenery and also offering side access to the 3-bay powered shed. </p>
<p>There are three bedrooms all with new carpet, the master including air-conditioning and built-in wardrobe. A contemporary bathroom services the household impeccably and includes a bath for family use. </p>
<p>A central position ensures that shopping and dining is only minutes away. Schooling is in abundance, both private and state. The perfect opportunity for immediate liveability whilst offering scope to upgrade in the future.</p>
<p>&#8211; 655m2 block<br />
&#8211; Fully fenced<br />
&#8211; 3 bay shed<br />
&#8211; Split level home<br />
&#8211; Timber floors<br />
&#8211; Air-conditioned living, dining and master bedroom<br />
&#8211; Covered outdoor entertaining area with great privacy plus huge backyard<br />
&#8211; Three bedrooms<br />
&#8211; Well-appointed family bathroom<br />
&#8211; Off-street parking plus gated side access</p>
<p>So close to:<br />
&#8211; Sandgate, the cutest bayside village centre in greater Brisbane<br />
&#8211; Bike and footpaths stretching the length of the waterfront linking to parks, nature reserves cafés, a brand-new aquatic centre and historic Shorncliffe jetty<br />
&#8211; Specialty stores and all key services<br />
&#8211; Endless cafés, coffee shops and restaurants<br />
&#8211; Public and private schools<br />
&#8211; Public transport and easy access to the M1.<br />
&#8211; Sandgate dining shopping precinct and Sandgate Train Station for the short commute to Brisbane city, is 5 minutes by car.<br />
&#8211; Brisbane Airport is 15 minutes by car</p>
<p>Properties with this much potential and in such a great location don&#8217;t come around often, so ensure you contact me today!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>57/154 Goodfellows Road, Murrumba Downs  QLD  4503</title>
		<link>https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/57-154-goodfellows-road-murrumba-downs-qld-4503/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Image Property Management]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 04:42:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/57-154-goodfellows-road-murrumba-downs-qld-4503/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[With strict instructions to present all offers, you don&#8217;t want...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With strict instructions to present all offers, you don&#8217;t want to miss out on the opportunity to secure this property.  </p>
<p>Inside Features:<br />
&#8211;  Open plan kitchen, dining &#038; living areas provide plenty of room for the entire family<br />
&#8211;  Three bedrooms upstairs with the master bedroom boasting, walk-in robe, air-conditioning and ensuite<br />
&#8211;  Family bathroom<br />
&#8211;  Functional kitchen with plenty of bench space and storage<br />
&#8211;  Air-conditioning<br />
&#8211;  Built-in wardrobes throughout<br />
&#8211;  Separate internal laundry</p>
<p>Outside Features:<br />
&#8211;  Automatic lock-up garage and extra off-street parking<br />
&#8211;  Complex includes in-ground pool and BBQ area, perfect for Summer<br />
&#8211;  Covered outdoor entertaining area<br />
&#8211;  Large, fully fenced back yard </p>
<p>Located in the thriving suburb of Murrumba Downs, this quiet and highly sought after area has close access to the Bruce Highway, shopping centres, local schools and public transport (new rail 5 min walk) and all of the North Lakes amenities such as IKEA, Costco and Westfield.</p>
<p>Don&#8217;t miss out, call to arrange an inspection with our Team !</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>75 Albert Street, Margate  QLD  4019</title>
		<link>https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/75-albert-street-margate-qld-4019/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Image Property Management]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 04:42:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/75-albert-street-margate-qld-4019/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Are you looking for the ultimate dual living home in...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you looking for the ultimate dual living home in the heart of the beautiful Peninsula? Look no further than 75 Albert Street, Margate. </p>
<p>Perched on a grand, fully fenced 415sqm block in a quiet leafy street sits this beautiful, freshly renovated, modern 2-bedroom home with an added granny flat for the ultimate dual living potential. </p>
<p>The house contains two good size bedrooms where the master bedroom is built with a great built-in wardrobe for the ultimate storage. A fresh bathroom with a separate toilet and a laundry located to the rear of the home.</p>
<p>The open plan living sees you in the large, recently renovated kitchen which boasts plenty of bench and storage space. The kitchen flows out onto the great closed in, private deck, perfect for entertaining. </p>
<p>From the kitchen you overlook the living space which is surrounded by windows so you can relax in your own haven with the beautiful sea breezes, looking out onto the leafy surroundings. </p>
<p>With polished timber floors and fitted with ceiling fans through and air-conditioning in the living room, there isn&#8217;t a single feature missed in this home&#8230;. But wait, there is more.</p>
<p>Leaving the rear of the house you are standing in your own grassy hidden hide away which leads you to the grand granny flat. </p>
<p>Beautifully renovated, and finished with modern touches, this will be the ultimate teenagers retreat or guest house. With its own kitchen and great big private, outdoor space, this is heaven. Off the private outdoor area sits, a trendy little caravan for extra bedding or hang out spaces. </p>
<p>With features such as side access, outdoor fireplace, a garage, and a shed for ample storage, plenty of off-street parking, water tanks, solar panels, and dimming lights&#8230; the list goes on. </p>
<p>What more could you want? Be sure to come and see it for yourself before this property is snatched up.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>1/52 Susan Avenue, Kippa-Ring  QLD  4021</title>
		<link>https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/1-52-susan-avenue-kippa-ring-qld-4021/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Image Property Management]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 04:42:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/1-52-susan-avenue-kippa-ring-qld-4021/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Just a short walk to Kippa-Ring shopping centre with everything...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Just a short walk to Kippa-Ring shopping centre with everything from medical to cinemas, transport to food outlets, bus and new train station nearby. Ideal low maintenance home or great investment in a sort-after location. </p>
<p>With only one neighbour, this low maintenance duplex with a brand new roof, renovated kitchen and bathroom and plenty of yard is a must see!</p>
<p>Features Include:<br />
* Renovated kitchen with stone bench tops and stainless steel appliances<br />
* Modern bathroom<br />
* Two bedrooms with built in wardrobes<br />
* Great size lounge room with reverse cycle air conditioning<br />
* Separate laundry<br />
* Large fully fenced yard<br />
* Fully fenced yard, perfect for the kids or pet<br />
* Single lock up garage<br />
* Courtyard<br />
* Freshly re-pointed and painted roof as well as new gutters<br />
* Solar Power</p>
<p>*Low body corporate fees approximately $287 per quarter<br />
*Council rates $404 per quarter<br />
*Water rates approximately $312 per quarter</p>
<p>Properties like this don&#8217;t come up very often to be sure to get in quick!<br />
For more information please contact Matt Phillips or Sophie Maiden!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>1&#038;2/20 Acqua Street, Burpengary  QLD  4505</title>
		<link>https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/12-20-acqua-street-burpengary-qld-4505/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Image Property Management]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 04:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://imageproperty.com.au/homes-for-sale/12-20-acqua-street-burpengary-qld-4505/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[&#8220;If applicable &#8211; check out the virtual tour tools available...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;If applicable &#8211; check out the virtual tour tools available for this property, as well as the 3D tool button or External Links button to access them.&#8221; </p>
<p>This is a must see property for anyone looking to build their portfolio by investing in Real Estate located between Brisbane and the Sunshine Coast and 30 mins to the white sands of Bribie Island. </p>
<p>Located in the Acacia Estate, surrounded with all conveniences one could need, with close access to the Aquatic &#038; Sport Centre, highway access, public transport and major shopping centres – this will be a high demand investment property always. With immaculate presentation and quality fixtures and fittings throughout, this 5-bedrooms, 3 bathrooms, 2 car lockup duplex has plenty to offer, along with the benefits of NO Body corporate fees payable.</p>
<p>Unit 1 features Include:<br />
* Main bedroom with ensuite<br />
* 2 bedrooms with built in wardrobes<br />
* Separate main bathroom<br />
* Open plan kitchen, lounge and dining room<br />
* Open style kitchen with modern appliances and gas cooktop<br />
* Air conditioned in master bedroom and main living area<br />
* Ceiling fans throughout<br />
* Internal laundry<br />
* Single lock up garage with remote<br />
* Covered alfresco<br />
* Security screens to windows and doors<br />
* Low maintenance yard</p>
<p>Unit 2 features Include:<br />
* 2 bedrooms with built-in wardrobes<br />
* Open plan kitchen, lounge and dining room<br />
* Air conditioned and ceiling fans throughout<br />
* Internal laundry<br />
* Galley kitchen with modern appliances and ceramic cooktop<br />
* Single lock up garage with remote<br />
* Security screens to windows and doors<br />
* Covered alfresco<br />
* Gas hot water<br />
* Intercoms for added security<br />
* Well presented with low maintenance yard with the rear fully fenced</p>
<p>Noticeable Features:<br />
Minutes to Aquatic &#038; Sports Centre<br />
Minutes to Highway access<br />
5 minutes to Burpengary &#038; Morayfield Shopping Centres<br />
5 kms to Burpengary &#038; Morayfield Railway Stations<br />
Public &#038; Private Primary &#038; High Schools close by<br />
No Body Corp fees<br />
Built 2015 on 600m2</p>
<p>Information contained on any marketing material, website or other portal should not be relied upon and you should make your own enquiries and seek your own independent advice with respect to any property advertised or the information about the property.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
